Marvin C. Griffin papers, Inclusive: 1940-2011, undated, Bulk: 1960-1999, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Subject Files, 1943-2011, undated; 3
  - Masonic Lodge, undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Collected Music, 1945-1952 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - The New Century Pastoral Academy, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - National Baptist Publishing Board Meetings, 1972-1976 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - National Baptist Publishing Board Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - National Congress of Christian Workers Financial, 1989-2003 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Poetry, circa 1960s-1980s (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Travel, undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Statistician’s Reports, 1967-1980 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Statistician’s Reports, 1983-1997 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Sex, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Pan Texas Mortgage Investment Company, 1969-1974 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Ebenezer Child Development Center, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Progressive Voter’s League Clippings, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Preaching, undated (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Pastor’s Conference, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Pastoral Letters, 1959-1969 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Politics Message, undated (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - St. John Regular Baptist Association District Congress, 1987-2001 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Sunday School Lectures, undated (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Sunday School Teaching Materials, undated (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Sunday School Training and Meetings, 1954-1969 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Texas Southern University Board of Directors Meetings, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Topology, undated (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Teaching the Black Experience, undated (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Teacher Training (1 of 5), undated (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Teacher Training (2 of 5), undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Teacher Training (3 of 5), undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Teacher Training (4 of 5), undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Teacher Training (5 of 5), undated (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Training Union Suggestions, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Vietnam, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - West Africa, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Woman, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - County Commissioner, 1974-1985 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Community National Bank, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - New Testament I, Dr. Craig [RESTRICTED], 1943-1945 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Lesson Notebooks, circa 1946 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Church Art and Architecture, 1945-1946 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Reformation, Dr. Michaelides, 1945 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Rural Church, Dr. L.A. Stidley [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Church History I and II, Dr. T.S. Kepler [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Letters Received, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Letters, 1927-1969 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Christian Education, 1959-1963 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Employment, 1963-1964 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Evangelism, undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Deacon, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Grand Jury Association, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Israel, 1962-1964 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Written Letters, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Guyana, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Young Men’s Christian Association (1 of 7), 1953-1964 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Young Men’s Christian Association (2 of 7), 1953-1964 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Young Men’s Christian Association (3 of 7), 1953-1964 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Young Men’s Christian Association (4 of 7), 1953-1964 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Young Men’s Christian Association (5 of 7), 1953-1964 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Young Men’s Christian Association (6 of 7), 1953-1964 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Young Men’s Christian Association (7 of 7), 1953-1964 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Greek Orthodox Church, Dr. Michaelides, 1945 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Civil Rights, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood, 1954-1955 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Ministers Union of Waco and McLennan County, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - School Advisory Committee, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Anti-Crime Council of Texas, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Church Administration, 1946-1951 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Pastoral Qualifications, undated (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Advanced Parish Ministers’ Colloquy, 1959-1960 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Progressive Community Council, 1963-1965 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Pastor In Training, 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Old Testament-Jeremiah Term Paper, undated (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - State Congress of Christian Workers Ministers’ Department, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Marriage, undated (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Waco Clubs, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Action Planning Council, 1961-1966 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Action Planning Council, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Waco Public Library, 1961-1964 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Urban Renewal, 1958-1965 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - World Council of Churches Clippings, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Union Baptist Association, 1964-1968 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Waco Ministerial Association, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Ushers, undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Race Relations, 1963-1965 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Texas Employment Commission, 1963-1965 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Texas Southern University Board of Directors, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Texas Southern University Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Southwest Educational Development Laboratory, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Waco Park Board, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Christian Ethics, Oberlin Graduate School of Theology, 1946 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Recommendations, 1951-1955 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Revival, undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Educational Principles, Dr. Heacock [RESTRICTED], 1954 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Women’s Missionary Union, 1951-1956 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Ethics, Missions and History Essays for Dr. Horton and Dr. Buckler [RESTRICTED], circa 1947 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Class Syllabi by Marvin Griffin, undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Missions, Dr. Hamilton [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Psychology of Christian Character, Dr. Horton [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Social Problems, Professor L. Owens [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Director of Baptist Fellowship Center, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Philosophy of Religion, Dr. C.H. Hamilton [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Christian Education, undated (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Religious Education, Dr. Stidley [RESTRICTED], 1944-1945 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Religious Education II, Dr. Stidley [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Building A Church, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Old Testament I and II, Dr. H. G. May [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Contemporary Philosophy of Religion, Dr. C.H. Hamilton, 1946 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - The Troubadours-Publicity Programs, 1945-1946 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Religion of Israel, Dr. H.G. May [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - New Testament VII, Dr. T.S. Kepler [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - New Hope Baptist Church, undated (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - “The Need for Expansion of the City-County Industrial School to Include Services for Negros” by J.S. Cosby, undated (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - History of Religions I, Dr. Hamilton [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Old Testament, Dr. H.G. May [RESTRICTED], 9144-1945 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Comments on Sunday School Lessons, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Comments on Sunday School Lessons, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Comments on Sunday School Lessons, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Comments on Sunday School Lessons, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Comments on Sunday School Lessons, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Marriage Ceremonies, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Money Management for Preachers, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Jubilee Advance, 1962-1964 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Discussion Topics, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Collected Papers and Lectures, 1954-1969 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Educational Principles, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Pecan Springs School, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Bishop College Report and Recommendations (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Bishop College Report and Recommendations (2 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Waco Model City Program, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Sunday School Lessons, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Collected Clippings, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Teaching the Bible, undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Recreational Programs, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - National Baptist Convention-Historian Materials, 1959-1963 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Dying Testimony, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Youth Committee of Waco, 1953 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Youth Activities Calendar, 1951-1958 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Youth Movement, 1951-1952 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Worship Suggestions, 1944-1950 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Baptists in Russia Study, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Missionaries and New Members, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Religious Psychology, undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha, undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - “Old Testament Hermeneutics” by P.H. Williams Jr., 1981 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - San Antonin Metro Alliance, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Philosophy of Christianity, Dr. W.M. Horton, undated (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Blackness Is, undated (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Prayer for House of Representatives, 1992 November 18 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical Breakfast at the White House, 1997 November 20 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Vita for Dr. Harold Thompson, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Christmas, undated (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - True Greatness, undated (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - National Urban Enterprise Zones (1 of 3), 1993 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - National Urban Enterprise Zones (2 of 3), 1993 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - National Urban Enterprise Zones (3 of 3), 1993 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Christian Life Commission Report, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Woman’s Day, 1985 May 19 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Report to National Baptist Convention of America by Dr. James Carl Sams, President, undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Teaching at Southwestern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Collected Minutes, undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church Correspondence, 1974-2010, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Marvin C. Griffin Biographical Sketches and Family History, 2010, undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Griffin Family Correspondence, 1955-2011 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - “Hall Johnson-Preserver of the Old Negro Spiritual” by Marva Griffin Carter, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Griffin Family Birth and Death Certificates, 1982-2009 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Marvin C. Griffin Retirement-Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1991-1994 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Marvin C. Griffin Rent and Property Records, 1980-1984 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Marvin C. Griffin Legal Materials, 2009-2012 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - St. John Regular Baptist Association Financial Report, 1979-1980 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Marvin C. Griffin Orthopedic History Sheet, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Marvin C. Griffin Financial-Boston University, 1974-1978 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Griffin Family-Financial (1 of 2), 1963-2009 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Griffin Family-Financial (2 of 2), 1963-2009 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Notebook, General, undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Clipping: New York Times: “Black Declaration of Independence”, 1970 July 3 (Box [1063] OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Award: Outstanding Leadership: Texas Southern University Board of Directors: Marvin C. Griffin, 1966 August 11 (Box [1063] OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Diploma: Bishop College: Bachelor of Arts: Marvin C. Griffin, 1943 December 4 (Box [1063] OVZ, Folder 3)
- Audio-Visual Materials, 1940-2010, undated; 4
  The Audio-Visual Materials include mostly video tapes, reels and cassette tapes of sermons given by Marvin C. Griffin and other prominent Baptist pastors. There are some photographs and scrapbooks as well. Researchers should reference the supplementary document attached to this finding aid for a complete list of the cassette tapes in this series. The series is in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  35 mm slide; Cassette tape; Compact disk (CD); Photographic print; Postcards; Reel to reel tapes; Video home system (VHS) tapes
  - Postcards from Brazil, circa 1950s (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Plaque: Kennedy-Boyce Award: Marvin C. Griffin, 2007 June 10 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Plaque: Southwestern Baptist Theological Seminary: First Black Graduate: Marvin C. Griffin, 1991 Spring (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook: Ebenezer Extra: Ebenezer Baptist Church, 2001 December-2002 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook: Marvin C. Griffin (1 of 3), 1941-1955, undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook: Marvin C. Griffin (2 of 3), 1941-1955, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook: Marvin C. Griffin (3 of 3), 1941-1955, undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook: Marvin C. Griffin: Loose Materials (1 of 4), 1940-1986, undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook: Marvin C. Griffin: Loose Materials (2 of 4), 1940-1986, undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook: Marvin C. Griffin: Loose Materials (3 of 4), 1940-1986, undated (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook: Marvin C. Griffin: Loose Materials (4 of 4), 1940-1986, undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Marvin C. Griffin, undated (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Slides: General, undated (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Slides: Israel, undated (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Audio Recordings: Compact Disc: “Growing Old Gracefully”: Marvin C. Griffin: Ebenezer Baptist Church, 2008 September 28 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Audio Recordings: Compact Disc: “God Gave Noah the Rainbow Sign”: Marvin Griffin: Ebenezer Baptist Church, 2010 March 2 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Audio Recordings: Compact Disc: “The Church Pergamos”: Marvin C. Griffin: Ebenezer Baptist Church, 2010 March 9 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Audio Recordings: Video Tape: Austin Metropolitan Ministries, undated (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Audio Recordings: Video Tape: “Ebenezer Baptist and First Baptist, Wimberley Joint Service”, 1992 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Audio Recordings: Video Tape: Ebenezer Village: TV News Coverage, 1996 June 22 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Audio Recordings: Video Tape: “Take a Closer Look, Baylor”, undated (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Audio Recordings: Video Tape: “Tear Down the Walls”: Fifth Annual Awards Ceremony: TFV Ministry, 2000 December 16 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: Unidentified, undated (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Audio Recordings: Video Tape: “Stone of Help” (1 of 2), 1999 December (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Audio Recordings: Video Tape: “Stone of Help” (2 of 2), 1999 December (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Moses” and “Elijah”, 1961 September 24, undated (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Jacob” and “Jeremiah”, 1961 November 19 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Adversity” and “Hearing Voices”, 1962 February 4, undated (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Youth Day Speaker” and “Dr. William Holmes Borders”, 1962 March 4 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Wonderful Counselor” and “The Space Age Family” and “What Does God Require” and “Dividing the Inheritance”, 1963 December 8-1969 November 8 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “The Best Investment” and “Religious Concert by Mrs. Beulah A. Curry”, 1965 November 28 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Woman’s Day Program by Barbara Gordon” and “Rev. D.A. Williams” and “Me Dear IsEL” and “Rev. Rould” and “Usher Day” and “Roosevelt High Choir” and “Rev. Barter’s Anniversary”, 1967 May 21-1969 January 25 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “The Quest for Identity” and “God Will Provide”, 1969 October 19-November 16 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “A Strong Man’s Weakness” and “Men’s Day Fellowship” and “A Creative Minority” and “Young Adult Choir Program”, 1971 August-1972 April (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “An Attitude of Gratitude” and “Youth Organizations” and “Coming of Age”, 1969 November 23-30 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Looking Back” and “Saved by Hope” and “Leap to the Lord”, 1969 December 28-1970 January 11 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Revolutionary Troops” and “Bankrupts Before God” and “Ushers’ Annual Sermon” and Good News for the Disinherited”, 1970 January 18-February 1 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Who is My Neighbor?” and “Beyond the Boundary” and “Gospel Choir”, 1970 February 8-22 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “The Cost of Discipleship” and “Search for Happiness” and “Life’s Learning Tree” and “Rev. T.M. Batts at New Sardis Primitive Baptist Church”, 1970 March 1-August 23 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Promise of Paradise”, 1970 March 8 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Woman’s Day Observance on Being the Right Size” and “O Come Let Us Worship” and “Dr. J.J. Seabrook” and “Bargaining with God”, 1970 May 17-June 28 (Box 75 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Sing Unto God” and “Enough is Enough” and “Redigging Old Wells” and “Stop! Look! Listen!”, 1970 May 25-June 14 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Come Home” and “Service of Gratitude” and “Rev. Hector J. Grant” and “Men’s Day Program by Robert Darden”, 1970 July 5-August 9 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “The Right to Happiness” and “King of the Road” and “Seven Wonders” and “Stages on Life’s Way”, 1970 August 30-September 20 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “False Faces” and “Taming of the Tongue” and “Eyes that See” and “Be Thankful”, 1970 November 1-22 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “On Hearing What God Says” and “Waiting” and “Promises to Keep” and “The Rainbow Sign”, 1970 November 29-1971 July 25 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “God with Us” and “Lest We Forget” and “Seeking Bread But Finding Stones” and “Black Liberation and White Power”, 1970 December 20-1971 January 10 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “All or Nothing at All” and “Liberation and Reparation” and “The Long Way Home” and “Love is Something You Do”, 1971 January 31-February 21 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Stand Still and See Salvation” and “Operation Breadbasket” and “Crisis of the Cross” and “Senior Houston-Tilloston College by Rev. Henry B. Williams”, 1971 February 28-March 21 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Faces Around the Cross” and “Going to Jerusalem” and “Easter Clothes” and “Turned On”, 1971 March 28-April 18 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Honest to God” and “Wholeness in a Broken World” and “God’s Family” and “A New Kind of Woman”, 1971 April 25-May 16 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Adam’s Rib” and “Chaplain Connie Stamps” and “Christ in Me” and “Summer Fruit”, 1971 June 27-July 18 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Lost” and “Wash Me” and “Judgment Day” and “God in the World of Work”, 1971 August 1-September 5 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Rev. Mathis Dickson” and “Rev. White” and “Rev. Hector Grant” and “I Woke Up in Love This Morning”, 1971 September 12-26 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “He Keeps Me Singing” and “Faith to Move Mountains” and “The Call” and “The Name Above Every Name”, 1971 September 26-October 17 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Do What You Got to Do” and “God’s Trombones” and “Look Homeward Angel” and “Rev. L.V. Harvey”, 1971 October 24-31 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Cure for the Crisis” and “Run On”, 1971 November 7-14 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Think and Thank” and “Rev. Booker”, 1971 November 21-28 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Journey’s End” and “Future Shock and Saving Hope” and “Hold On” and “Rev. Bacon”, 1971 December 26-1972 January 23 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Being Born Again” and “Mary and Martha” and “Jesus Christ, The Bridge Over Troubled Waters” and “Youth Week”, 1972 February 27-March 12 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Bishop College Choir” and “Caiaphas and the Cross” and “Church Choir” and “The Third Day”, 1972 March 19-April 2 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “A New Future” and “Holy Helpers” and “Wine for the Wedding” and “The Road Through the Desert”, 1972 April 9-30 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “The Burning Bush” and “A Feast in the Wilderness” and “Rods and Serpents” and “Gone is the Glory” and “Honest to God” and “Signs of the Spirit”, 1978 February 5-April (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Forgetting the Deliverer” and “Christ the Rock” and “Transcending Our Limits” and “Passing the Test” and “Don’t Let the Cold World Get You” and “Turning Water Into Wine” and “Playboy Samson” and “Water from Leaking Buckets”, 1978 July 9-August 20 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Who Shall Rule Over the Trees” and “Where Shall We Buy Bread” and “Keep Moving by Rev. George Williams” and “Conquering the Giants”, 1978 September 3-17 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “You Light Up My Life” and “If God is Dead” and “Dialect of Deceit” and “The Good Shepherd” and “Dove Made My Vow” and “God We Make and The God Who Made Us” and “God’s No Fault Insurance”, 1978 September 27-October 15 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Keeping Cool in the Heat” and “Deliverance from the Lions’ Den”, 1979 September 16-23 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “A Friend at Midnight” and “Use It or Lose It”, 1979 September 30-November 11 (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Installation”, undated (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Rev. Marvin C. Griffin” (1 of 2), undated (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Rev. Marvin C. Griffin” (2 of 2), undated (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - Audio Recordings: Reel-to-Reel: “Rev. R.L. Rowe”, undated (Box 76 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 62 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 77 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 61 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 78 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 79 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 80 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 81 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 82 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 83 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 84 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 85 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 86 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 87 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 88 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 89 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 90 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 91 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 92 OVZ)